(Leonard:)Yes! First place.
(Leonard:)I would have been a great jockey
if I weren't too tall.
(Leonard:)And scared of horses.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're up.
(Sheldon:)- What?
- Come on, it's your turn.
(Leonard:)We said we'd get more fresh air.
(Sheldon:)Sorry. I'm a little distracted.
I can't seem to get in touch with Amy.
(Sheldon:)I tried e-mail, video chat,
tweeting her...
(Sheldon:)...posting on her Facebook Wall,
texting her, nothing.
(Leonard:)Did you try calling her
on the telephone?
(Leonard:)The telephone.
(Sheldon:)You know, Leonard,
in your own simple way...
(Sheldon:)...you may be the wisest of us all.
Voicemail.
Tsk. Curiouser and curiouser.
(Leonard:)If you're worried,
we can go and see if she's all right.
(Penny:)Okay.
You know, I heard in the news...
(Sheldon:)...a bobcat has been spotted
in her neighborhood.